{
    "subject": "resource/Jamais_(song)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jamais_(song)",
    "human_readable": "Jamais is primarily about 'Jamais_(song)'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.952174961566925,
            "question": "What is Jamais primarily about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.939370334148407,
            "question": "Is Jamais a song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.820985734462738,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the song Jamais?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8067173361778259,
            "question": "Are there any notable lyrics from Jamais?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6529533863067627,
            "question": "Is there a music video for Jamais?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5515069365501404,
            "question": "Who created or performed Jamais?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5337996482849121,
            "question": "What genre does Jamais belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5084554553031921,
            "question": "What type of work is Jamais?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5061785578727722,
            "question": "Where can I listen to Jamais?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4564555287361145,
            "question": "When was Jamais released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jamais is primarily about 'Jamais_(song)'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1718_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I listen to Jamais?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1718_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is Jamais?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1718_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does Jamais belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1718_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1718_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that \"Jamais\" is primarily about the song, as they discuss various aspects and meanings of the song with this title."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}